

CONTACT

Phone:

+381 63/140-64-25

Email:

civcicboris93@gmail.co

Website:

www.civcic.com

Address:

Sijekovac 80, 74450 Bosanski Brod, BiH

PRO SKILLS

HTML5/CSS3

React.JS

Shopify

WordPress

Webpack

CI/CD

TDD

BORIS CIVCIC

Front-End Developer - React.JS

I work as a Frontend Developer for about 6 years now.

Highly interested in building scalable, maintainable software with hight-quality code and one time delivery. The main reason why I am good at it is because I'm a passionate learner, always seeking for interesting and challenging work and most of all I care about my customer's interest.

EXPERIENCE

NOV.2018 - APRIL 2019 FULL-TIME REMOTE

ZOJAX GROUP

Front-End developer

As a full-time Web Developer at Zojax I have worked as a part of the development team.

JAN.2017 - NOV 2018 PART-TIME REMOTE

LOVAPPY

Team Lead Front-End Developer

Like a lead developer, I did more than 90% of the website.

- UI/UX design
- JavaScript(Ajax to include rest API)

JUL.2017 - AVG.2018 FULL-TIME REMOTE

IOV

React.JS Developer

React javascriot, Redux, actions, reducers, axios, redux-thunk, middlaware, webpack, npm

JAN.2016 - MAY2017 FULL-TIME REMOTE

SOCKAM

React.JS Developer

React javascriot, Redux, actions, reducers, axios, redux-thunk, middlaware, webpack, npm, UI/UX

NOV.2014- JAN.2016 FULL-TIME REMOTE

ZOJAX GROUP

JavaScript(Angular 1.x) Developer

PSD - to HTML, include new features, payment system(paypal), login/register etc...

NOV.2013 - OCT.2014 NOVI SAD, SERBIA

DEGREE 361

Wordpress Developer

Proficient and creative WordPress developer with a strong history in website management and development.

FEB.2012 - OCT.2013 NOVI SAD, SERBIA

ENTYPO

Front-End Developer

Developed fully functional responsive prototypes based on Business Requirements using HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript

EDUCATION

2008 - 2012 BOSANSKI BROD, BIH

HIGH ELECTRICAL ENGINEERING

School Nikola Tesla, Bosanski Brod

Porttitor amet massa Done cporttitor dolor enisl mlestie the ium feliscon lore tfringilla.

REFERENCE

MARK NEJMEH

Lovappy Group Phone: (732) 995-3914 Email: mark@lovappy.com MARKO DIMITRIJEVIC

Level Up 018

Email: dmarko@superspace.se